// Quesitons for Harry Potter Category
// One object for each question
// Array holding all objects

const hpQuestions = [
   {
      "question": "What do Hermione's parents do for a living?",
      "correctAns": "Dentists",
      "multChoice": ["Green Grocers", "Dentists", "Bankers", "Chiropractors", "Drill Manufacturers"]
   },

   {
      "question": "Which of these was not a monster that Harry faced in the maze in the Third Task of the Triwizard Tournament?",
      "correctAns" : "Grindylow",
      "multChoice" : ["Sphinx", "Skrewt", "Boggart", "Grindylow", "Spider"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "What is Percy's Owl's name?",
      "correctAns" : "Hermes",
      "multChoice" : ["Hermes", "Errol", "Abraxas", "Arnold", "Roonil"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "What form was Ernie Macmillan's Patronus?",
      "correctAns" : "Boar",
      "multChoice" : ["Hare", "Otter", "Thestral", "Rat", "Boar"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "Who of the following was never a member of the Order of the Phoenix?",
      "correctAns" : "",
      "multChoice" : ["Nymphadora Tonks", "Severus Snape", "Horace Slughorn", "Elphias Doge", "Aberforth Dumbledor",]
   },

   {
      "question" : "What is Dean Thomas' favorite Football (soccer) team?",
      "correctAns" : "West Ham United",
      "multChoice" : ["West Ham United", "Wolverhampton Wanderers", "Manchester United", "Everton", "A.F.C. Richmond"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "How many 'Outstanding' O.W.L.'s did Hermione receive?",
      "correctAns" : "10",
      "multChoice" : ["11", "14", "13", "10", "21"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "What street does Severus Snape live on?",
      "correctAns" : "Spinner's End",
      "multChoice" : ["Privet Drive", "Mongolia Crescent", "Spinner's End", "Charring Cross Road", "Grimmauld Place"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "What model broomstick does Ron receive in Order of the Phoenix?",
      "correctAns" : "Cleansweep Eleven",
      "multChoice" : ["Nimbus Two-Thousand", "Cleansweep Eleven", "Comet Two-Sixty", "Shooting Star", "Bluebottle"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "How many staircases are there at Hogwarts?",
      "correctAns" : "142",
      "multChoice" : ["68", "394", "188", "208", "142"]
   },
]

export {
   hpQuestions
}